Hey, Rach, listen.
Did you know
that during pregnancy
your fingers swell
up to twice their size
and never go back?
Oh, my God.
Let me see that.
You fall for it every time.
Hey.
Look, I brought you
my old maternity clothes.
Oh, Pheebs, that's so sweet.
Oh, those are so cute.
And look.
See how they expand
as the baby grows?
And then, after
the baby's born
they're great for
shoplifting melons.
Oh, good, you're all here.
Okay, Thanksgiving
tomorrow, 4:00.
Oh.
And guess who I invited?
Remember that guy,
Will Colbert from high school?
No.
He was in Ross's class.
Marching band,
was kind of overweight.
Well, really overweight.
I mean, I was his thin friend.
Wow, I don't
remember him.
Honey, are you sure
you're not talking
about your
imaginary boyfriend?
No, that was Jarod.
Wow. Haven't thought
about him in a long time.
Anyway, Will's...
Will's here on business
and he didn't haves
a place to go
so I invited him here.
Well, that's nice.
Oh, and by the way
he's lost a bunch of weight.
I mean, he looks good.
Okay, I mean really,
really gorgeous.
( clearing throat )
I still love Chandler.
Wouldn't hurt you
to say it once in a while.
All right, okay, also,
just so you'll know--
I'm not going to make
a turkey this year.
What?
Well...
Phoebe doesn't
eat turkey.
Phoebe!
Turkeys are beautiful,
intelligent animals.
No, they're not. They're ugly,
and stupid and delicious.
All right, it's not just Phoebe.
Will's still on a diet.
Chandler doesn't eat
Thanksgiving food
and Rachel's having
her aversion to poultry.
She is?
Yeah. Don't you remember I had
to leave the room the other day
when you had that
roast chicken?
Yeah, but I thought
that was just 'cause
I put the whole thing on my hand
and made it walk
across the table.
Anyway, it just
doesn't seem worth it
to make a whole turkey
for just three people, okay?
It's a lot of work.
But you got to have
turkey on Thanksgiving.
I mean, Thanksgiving with
no turkey is like, like...
Fourth of July
with no apple pie
or, or Friday
with no two pizzas.
All right, fine, if it
means that much to you
but there's going to
be a ton left over.
No, there won't. I promise
I will finish that turkey.
All right, you're telling me
you can eat almost
an entire turkey
in one sitting?
That's right.
'Cause I'm a Tribbiani.
This is what we do.
I mean, we may not
be great thinkers
or world leaders.
We don't read a lot
or run very fast
but, damn it, we can eat!
♪ So no one told you
life was gonna be this way ♪
♪ Your job's a joke,
you're broke ♪
♪ Your love life's D.O.A. ♪
♪ It's like you're always
stuck in second gear ♪
♪ When it hasn't been
your day, your week ♪
♪ Your month,
or even your year ♪
♪ But I'll be there for you ♪
♪ 'Cause you're there
for me, too. ♪
Isn't it weird
to think about
how next year
at this time
there'll be a little baby
at the table?
Rachel's
but good to know
where you're at.
Hey!
Hey.
Happy Thanksgiving.
You, too.
Anything I can do to help?
Actually there is.
Chandler usually helps me
with this, but he's really
into the game,
so I don't want to bother him.
Could you help me
fold these napkins?
Sure.
I'm going to go across the hall
to check on the yams.
Okay.
Oh, no, no, no, sweetie.
No, not like that.
We're not
at a barn dance.
You want to fold them
like swans
like I showed you
at Christmastime, remember?
Yeah, it all just came
screaming back to me.
So, how's the game?
I have no idea.
What?
Yeah. I'm just pretending
to watch the game
so I don't have
to help out with stuff.
I don't believe you.
That is... brilliant.
And Monica has no idea?
Nope.
Every once in a while, I just
yell and scream stuff at the TV.
Hey! Oh, hey!
Is your team winning, hon?
Yeah, Anderson
just scored again.
There's no Anderson.
Well, I want to get in on this.
Hey, Mon, I don't think
I can help you after all.
I didn't realize
this game was on.
Oh. I didn't know
you liked football.
Well, normally I don't,
but, you know...
Green Bay is playing.
You like Green Bay?
Well, it's only,
like, my favorite bay.
( knocking )
Hey.
Happy Thanksgiving.
Oh, thanks.
God, Will, I'm so
glad that you came.
You look great.
You must have
lost, like...
150 pounds.
Yeah, I'm going to be
in one of those Subway
sandwich commercials.
A pie.
All right.
It's no fat, it's no
sugar, it's no dairy.
It's no good.
Throw it out.
You want to meet
some people?
This is, uh, this is
my husband Chandler.
Chandler, this is Will.
Hi.
Oh, hey. I'd shake your hand
but I'm really into the game.
Plus, I think it would
be better for my ego
if we didn't stand
right next to each other.
This is Phoebe.
Hi.
Hey.
Wow.
( gasps )
Well done.
Want to give me a hand?
Sure.
Monica, I can't get over
how great you look.
You look stunning.
You look incredible, too.
You're so fit.
I'm watching the game,
but I'm not deaf.
Oh, um, I meant to tell
you-- Ross is coming.
Ross is coming?
Great. I love Ross.
Good, and Rachel Green, too.
Ooh.
Is there a problem?
No. Uh...
It's okay. It's just, uh...
God, I hated her.
What?
Yeah, I hated her.
She was horrible to me
in high school...
but, hey,
it was a long time ago.
I'm in a good place.
It might be actually fun
to see her again.
Okay.
Got any cakes
or cookies or something?
No, Will. No.
You know, it's been a while
since we've screamed something.
Maybe we should.
Oh, okay.
Oh, come on!
No!
Damn you, ref!
You burn in hell!
Hey, what are
you doing?
You got to save room.
You've got almost
an entire turkey to eat.
Let me explain to you
how the human body works.
I have to warm up
my stomach first.
Eating chips is like stretching.
Okay.
Yeah. Don't worry,
Tribbianis never get full.
I actually know what
you're talking about
and I'm here to tell you
something, friend.
You can eat and eat and eat
but nothing will ever
fill that void.
Who the hell is this guy?
Will, from
high school. Joey.
Oh, hey.
Hello.
Will!
Ross.
Hey, you came.
Man, you look incredible.
Hot stuff!
"Hot stuff"?
It's good to see you, man.
Yeah, you, too.
Man, so, what
are you up to?
I'm a commodities broker.
Really? Yeah,
that-that sounds interesting.
Yeah, it's not.
Oh.
But I'm rich and thin.
Man, I don't think
I've seen you
since Lance Davis's
graduation party.
That was such
a fun night.
Yeah.
Would have been good
if we'd gotten in
but still, real fun.
Yeah.
God, we were
lame back then.
Do you remember how
into dinosaurs we were?
Yeah.
So, what do you...
what do you do now?
So, how long
are you in town?
Hi.
MONICA:
Hey, sweetie.
MONICA: Oh, good.
RACHEL: There you go.
Rachel Green.
Oh, oh,
that's right.
Are you going
to be okay?
Oh, I-I'll be fine.
It's just...
God, I hate her,
Ross. I hate her.
Okay.
Will, high school
was a long time ago.
Look at her standing
there with those yams.
My two greatest
enemies, Ross--
Rachel Green and
complex carbohydrates.
Oh, my God, Monica,
who is that?
That's Will,
from high school.
Oh. I do not remember him.
Wow, really got that sexy,
smoldering thing going on.
Oh, my God. He's...
Look at the way
he's just staring at me.
I think he's trying
to mouth something at me
but I can't make it out.
Okay, dinner's ready.
Good game.
Yeah.
Yeah, solid effort,
solid effort.
Oh, so who won?
Green Bay.
Detroit.
What?
Well, the Lions
technically won
but it was a moral victory
for the Green Bay... Mermen.
Hi.
Will, right?
Right.
Right. Hi,
I'm Rachel Green.
Oh, I remember you.
Really?
Mm-hmm.
Aren't you sweet?
I got to tell you,
though, I am...
I am having
the hardest time placing you.
Oh, oh, hang on.
I think I remember you.
Did we, um...
Did we fool around
at Lance Davis's
graduation party?
You are unbelievable.
Thank you.
Rachel, Rachel--
why don't you
sit here?
And, Will,
you sit way over there.
That's it?
Even if
nobody helps me
I can eat that,
no problem.
At least give me
a challenge.
( chuckling )
This is Chandler's chicken.
Ah.
This...
is the turkey.
Oh.
H-H-How big is that?
It's about 19 pounds.
That's like me
when I was born.
All right, who would
like some yams? Will?
Oh, you'd like that,
wouldn't you?
What?
No. You know what?
Can we please keep
the chicken and the turkey
and everything
on the other side
of the table?
The smell is just... yuck.
( coughs ):
Typical.
I'm sorry, what?
I said it was typical.
Typical of you,
Rachel Green, Queen Rachel.
Does whatever she wants
in little Rachel Land.
Seriously,
who is this guy?
( Rachel clears throat )
Sorry, uh, do you...
do you have a problem with me?
I don't know.
Do I? Do I?
I think you do.
Apparently, you were a little
mean to him in high school.
"A little mean"?
You made my life miserable.
I'm-I'm s...
I had no idea. I'm sorry.
Well, you should be.
Screw it. Bring on the yams.
Oh, Will, but you've
worked so hard...
Yams!
Okay.
RACHEL: Uh, Will,
I just want to say
that I'm real sorry
for whatever I-I did to you
in high school.
Oh, it wasn't just me.
We had a club.
You had a club?
That's right.
The I Hate Rachel Green Club.
Whoa, my God. So, what, you all
just joined together to hate me?
Who else was in this club?
Me... and Ross.
No need to point.
She knows who Ross is.
So, you were in an
"I Hate Rachel" Club?
Yes, he was.
No, no.
So, who else was in this "club"?
Actually, there was also
that exchange student
from Thailand
but I don't think
he knew what it was.
So, Ross, we went out
for two years
and you never told me you were
in an "I hate Rachel" club.
You went out with her?
We had a pact.
That was in high school.
It's not like
it was binding forever.
Then why did it have the word
"eternity" in it?
Okay, Monica,
did you know about this?
I swear I didn't.
Hey, is that why you guys
used to go up to your bedroom
and lock the door?
Yeah.
Mm, a little relieved,
I got to say.
Look, Rach, I'm sorry, okay?
I was a stupid kid, okay?
The only reason I joined...
Cofounded.
Cofounded...
Cofounded the club
was that I was insanely
in love with you.
Obviously, I didn't
handle it very well.
But if you think about it
the I Hate Rachel Club
was really
the I Love Rachel Club.
Uh, except that
it was really
the I Hate Rachel club.
Okay, so, what? You guys
would like get together
and like just say
mean things about me?
Well, we did a little
more than that.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
What, Will?
What else did you do?
We started a rumor.
What rumor?
Oh, come on, Will, just take off
your shirt and tell us.
Ross?
It's no big deal.
We-we... said that...
the rumor was
that, um...
you had both...
male and female
reproductive parts.
Ha!
What?
That's right.
We said your parents
flipped a coin
decided to raise you
as a girl
but you still had
a hint of a penis.
Oh, my God!
You started that?
What? You heard that?
Everyone in our
school heard it.
Everybody at my school heard it.
You were the hermaphrodite
cheerleader from Long Island?
Oh, no!
Oh, my God. This is all making
so much sense to me now.
This is why Adam Carter
wouldn't go out with me.
This is why Billy Trate
would just stay in this region.
Actually, Billy
Trate is gay now
so that one's not
really our fault.
Monica, how come
you never told me this?
I thought it might be true
and I was afraid
that you were going to cry
and then show it to me.
Joey, stop staring.
There's nothing there!
It's not true!
I'm afraid
I'm going to need proof.
Oh...!
( groans )
You are my Everest.
Joey, you don't
have to finish that.
Oh, yes, I do.
Otherwise what's next?
You know, today I'm just a guy
who can't finish a turkey
but tomorrow I'm the guy
who eats half a power bar
wraps up the rest
and puts it in the fridge?
No... no, I just...
I just got to change my pants.
What was I thinking?
Jeans have no give.
Okay, okay, listen to what
Sean McMann wrote in
my yearbook senior year.
"Dear Rach, you're
such a great person."
Not girl. "Person."
Rach, I think you're reading
a little too much into it.
"Dear Rach, you're
a great person.
Sorry about your
teeny weenie."
( laughing )
Look, what do you want me to do?
You want me to call everyone
in the entire school
and tell them it wasn't true?
Yes.
Could you also tell them
I'm skinny now?
Oh, me, too!
Well, look, I'm not
calling anybody, okay?
It was like a million years ago.
I don't care
how long ago it was.
You told people
that I was half-and-half.
You know what?
I just want to point out
I never did anything
to hurt you in high school.
That's not totally true.
What?
Well, you did start that rumor
about Ross making out
with Mrs. Altman
our 50-year-old librarian.
How did you know that?!
It's true?
No.
Yes, it is.
I saw you guys going at it
behind the card catalog.
( stammers )
Mrs. Altman?
She also made out
with Taka Ki Kek
the night before
he went back to Thailand.
I'm sorry, when you
were in high school
you made out with
50-year-old woman?
Hey, she didn't look 50.
Did she look 16?
Oh, there's a picture of her
in the yearbook actually.
Oh.
Wow.
She didn't photograph well.
Well, she probably wasn't
familiar with the process
having spent
most of her life
sitting for
oil paintings.
So, how did this happen?
Did she... did she lure you
to an early-bird dinner?
I was working late
in the library one afternoon.
It was just the two of us.
She needed some help
with her word jumble.
And...
one thing led to another.
If you must know,
Anita was very gentle
and tender.
May she rest in peace.
Didn't she walk with a cane?
Only when it was damp!
I can't believe
you-you told people about this.
Everybody knew?
You know what?
I'm back in the club.
Yeah!
I want to join!
What? Phoebe!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
But I never got to be in a club.
I didn't go to high school.
But three of us would meet
behind a dumpster
to learn French. Bonjour.
All right, fine.
You guys can have
your stupid little club
but I would just like to say
that what you did to me
is way worse
than what I did to you.
You gave me a teeny weenie.
( chuckling )
All right, listen.
You're just being silly.
Rachel, even with that rumor
you were one of the most
popular girls in school
and everyone wanted
to be like you.
One girl wanted
to be like you so much
she stuffed her pants
with a Tootsie Roll.
Wow...
And, Ross, if it weren't
for Rachel's rumor
no one in high school would've
even known who you were.
She put you on the map.
As a romancer
of the elderly.
Hey, Mrs. Altman
was the kind of woman
you could tell
she used to be pretty.
The eyes... they'd
still sparkle.
Guys, this stuff
is just so way in the past.
You've been through
so much since then.
And right now you've got
so more important stuff
going on in your lives.
Can't you just let this go?
( sighs )
She's right.
Yeah, I mean, we are
having a baby together.
Hold on.
You got her pregnant?
Yeah.
Are you getting married?
No.
So, you knocked her up,
but you're not going
to marry her?
Dude...
Anybody?
Okay.
It's exactly how
I imagined it would be.
All right, where's that turkey?
Joey, those are my
maternity pants.
No, no, these are my
Thanksgiving pants.
Well, that's it.
I'm done.
Whoo...
Oh, here come the meat sweats.
Well, Joey,
we're all...
we're all very
proud of you.
Yes, I believe we
can expect a call
from the president
any moment now.
Is there anything
we can do for you?
No, just nobody press
on my stomach.
You can keep those pants,
by the way.
Ooh, w-w-what do you got there?
Is that pie?
Yeah. You want some?
Ah, just cut me a little sliver.
A little bigger.
Bigger...
What? Are you afraid
you're going to run out?
Cut me real piece!